lovedgames.com 2015-12-20

# LovedGames.com

PLYmedia Solutions Inc., including its direct and indirect subsidiaries and affiliates or parent companies and their platform and services (together the “Company”), their respective websites (the “Websites”) and the services and technologies they provide (each, the “Services”) have a strong commitment to protect the privacy of its users. Our privacy policy aims to ensure the protection of privacy of our users and to provide them with control over the decision how their information is being used. 

#### Acceptance of Terms

By using or visiting the Websites or Services, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy (the “Policy”). If you do not agree with this Policy, please do not use the Websites or Services. This Policy should read together with the [Terms of Use](http://lovedgames.com/Terms.html) (or terms of use for the Services as may be available online or executed between the parties, together the “Terms”) and Copyright Policy which together comprise of the full agreement between the Company and its users. 

#### What this Policy Covers

This Policy covers “end-users” or Internet users, as opposed to our clients or subscribers. Some of our Services enable advertisers to provide you with advertising that is relevant to your interests and therefore, more useful to you. This Policy explains how we treat your privacy, so you may decide whether to benefit from our Services, including how you may opt-out. This Policy does not cover the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to people that we do not employ or manage, including any cookies placed from outside our services. 

#### Information Collection and Cookies

To help companies personalize the advertising to enhance ad effectiveness and relevancy, improve our Services, create new products or services, conduct research, and provide reporting for internal and external clients, we are required to use standard tracking technologies, such as cookies, local shared objects, and pixel tags to collect information about the way in which users may respond to, select and interact with an ad or any content provided therein, analyze usage patterns and record your browsing activity. Cookies are little bits of text that are set and accessed from within a browser on your computer. They are accessed to collect and send statistical information when a user returns to a website or goes to another website. Local shared objects (also known as “LSOs” or “Flash cookies”) are used by the authors of files that are read by Adobe Flash Player and the websites hosting those files in a similar manner as cookies, but can also be used for a variety of purposes such as keeping track of information you provided and remembering your preferences. To learn how to reject or delete LSOs, click [here](http://www.adobe.com/privacy/flash-player.html) for the Adobe Flash Player privacy policy. Pixel tags (also known as “web beacons” or “clear GIFs”) are often used in combination with cookies, and is a type of technology placed on a website for the purpose of tracking activity. We only use these tracking technologies to better target and analyze consumer behavior with the goal of enabling our clients to provide better and more relevant advertising. We do not use them to alter your Internet experience, other than to show you a targeted ad. 

WE DO NOT USE COOKIES OR ANY OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES TO PROCESS OR COLLECT ANY PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION ABOUT YOU. For purposes of this document, personally identifying information (PII) is information that personally identifies you and that is not otherwise publicly available, such as your first and last name, social security or identification number, credit card number, phone number, or email address. We use tracking technology for non-PII only, which is information that cannot be directly associated with a specific person or entity, such as your computer’s configuration, and the version and type of browser you are using. While some non-PII could be used in conjunction with other information to personally identify a user (e.g., the address of a web page or of a computer on the Internet could identify a user when combined with Internet service provider records), we ourselves generally have no way of tying any of the information we collect back to a particular user, and in the unusual circumstance that we could use an Internet protocol address for such purposes, we do not do so unless required by law. In some situations, you may be directed to an ad that requests you to complete some additional information about yourself, including PII. Any such collection may be done by the website from which you visited or the advertiser and PLYmedia shall not be liable or responsible for any collection of such or any information. 

#### Information Sharing and Disclosure

We do not rent or sell any information about you to others, or trade any such information. We may share aggregate information, and other non-PII information about you for various purposes, such as to perform or enhance our Services. We may also share any information (including to personally identify a user) with our affiliates or service providers, in response to any request by authorities that we believe legally compels us to respond, to establish or exercise legal rights or defend against legal claims, to investigate, prevent, or take action for violations of our terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law, or to transfer such information, subject to the terms of this Policy, if we were to acquire, or were acquired by or merged with, another company. 

#### International Data Transfer

We transfer your personal information as described in this Policy to the United States, where it is processed, collected and stored using Amazon Web Services, Inc., (“AWS”) a subsidiary of Amazon.com, Inc. or its affiliates and Google Cloud Services. The AWS Customer Agreement can be found AWS Customer Agreement can be found [here](http://aws.amazon.com/agreement/). The Google terms of service can be found [here](https://cloud.google.com/terms/) and [here](https://cloud.google.com/storage/sla): We take adequate measures to ensure the privacy of data subjects, and except as set forth in this Policy, we will not transfer your data to any other person, whether in the United States or in another country. We have submitted to be registered with the Israeli Registry, The Israeli Law, Information and Technology Authority (ILITA). More information on ILITA can be found [here](http://www.justice.gov.il/PrivacyGenerations/about_ilita.htm). 

#### Your Ability to Edit/Delete Your Information

Because we do not collect PII, and the information we obtain is automatic through tracking technologies, we cannot provide you the ability to edit or update your non-PII information after it is collected. You can always opt-out though. If you opt-out from tracking technologies, any information that we already have collected or stored may remain in back-up storage for some period of time after your deletion request, but in no event longer than a year. This may be the case even though no more information remains in our active databases. 

#### Privacy Opt-Out

You may further opt-out of providing information to us and through of our collection of non-PII from cookies placed on your computer, by clicking on the following URL: <http://ads.adk2.com/opt-out> .By clicking this opt-out link, we will no longer collect non-PII information from your website or users (from the domain adk2.com or plymedia.com). You may opt back in, by clicking on the following URL: <http://ads.adk2.com/opt-in>. 

#### User Consent

The best of our knowledge none of our properties employ software that is installed on a user’s computer or other electronic device without the user’s consent. Furthermore, our properties’ disclosure and removal policies with regard to any software that is installed on a user’s computer or other electronic device shall be reasonably clear and concise. We contractually assure that our publishers and affiliates maintain, on each of the properties, a privacy statement that (a) discloses the use of third-party advertising companies to serve ads on their property(s), which may, directly or indirectly, collect or use information about user visits to websites to display advertisements more tailored to users’ interests, and (b) includes language to the following effect: “If a user wishes to know more about this practice or would like to know more about his/her options, the user can visit the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) web-site: [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) or other similar industry associations for additional details. The NAI is a cooperative of online advertising companies who are committed to responsible practices and consumer protection.” 

#### Children

Our products and services are not designed for, or directed at children. We do not create segments to specifically target anyone under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect any information from them. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received information from a child under the age of 13, we will take all appropriate steps to delete such information from our records. 

#### Data Security and Retention

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Policy, please contact us at privacy@plymedia.com. 

#### Updates to this Policy

From time to time we may make changes to this Policy and publish the same prominently on our website with the date of last update. These changes will supersede any prior changes. You understand and agree that we will treat your continued use of our product or Websites or Services after such changes have been published as your acceptance of the updated Policy. 

#### Use of Metadata

The Company may use the metadata which is created in the process of creating, editing and sharing content to enrich its costumer’s experiences and provide its customers and affiliates with useful information, in accord with its Policy. The metadata is Company’s property and the Company reserves the right to share the metadata with its partners and affiliates. You are informed not to insert PII unless you understand and agree that such information may be shared. 

#### Disclaimer Regarding Linked Sites

While using the Services you may be linked from or to third party sites. We are not responsible for information, content, terms, offers or the privacy policies at these sites. When you use a link to go from our Website or Service to another website, this Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which has a link on or to our Websites, is subject to that website’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding. 

#### LAST UPDATED: July 2015
